&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：为了理解我想要的东西
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So to understand that thing that I would like there to be in
中间，我们面临的全有或全无的难题，
the middle, the all or nothing sort of conundrum that we're facing,
我想更具体地探究一下这些利弊。
I wanna dig into those pros and cons a little bit more specifically.
这些只是我对利弊的看法，这不是什么客观的清单。
These are just my takes on the pros and cons, this is not some objective list.
第一，我认为打字和流程这样的系统最大的优点之一，
Number one, I think one of the big pros about systems like TypeScript and Flow,
我之前说过，它们使类型在您的代码中更加明显。
I said this earlier, they make the types much more obvious in your code.
这是一个很大的进步。
And that's a big improvement.
与编写本质上完全不确定的代码相比，这是一个很大的改进，
A big improvement over writing code that's essentially completely uncertain,
无法确定这次行动会发生什么。
unascertainable what's gonna happen with this particular operation.
让这些类型变得明显是一件好事。
Making those types obvious is a good thing.
这也是一个很强的积极作用，打字稿的设计和
It's also a very strong positive that the design of TypeScript and
流动，把双关语放在这里，随波逐流，
Flow, to put a pun here, goes with the flow,
如果你愿意，看看静态类型在许多其他语言中的工作方式。
if you will, of the way static typing works in a lot of other languages.
语法非常相似。
The syntaxes are very similar.
所以有一种强烈的熟悉感。
And so there's a strong sense of familiarity.
当你出现在这样的事情上，你并不是完全不同的
When you show up to something like that, you're not in this entirely different
世界比你以前做过的类型更多。
world than you've ever done with types before.
它感觉非常像你从更多的
It feels very much like the types that you have from a more
典型的类型化语言，如Java或C+。
typically typed language, like a Java or C++.
所以熟悉是一个很强的专业，我相信这是他们设计的一部分。
So the familiarity is a strong pro, and I'm sure that was part of their design.
他们非常受欢迎。
They are extremely popular.
不可否认，尤其是打字稿的受欢迎程度。
It's undeniable the popularity, especially of TypeScript.
似乎每天我们都会收到一些新的主要开放源码的公告
It seems like everyday we get an announcement of some new major open source
完全转换成打字稿的项目。
project that's completely converting over to TypeScript.
就像在某件事背后在社区中建立起来的炒作曲线一样
And just like the hype curves that build up in the community behind something
就像REACT或VUE一样，他们以如此强大的方式建立起来，有很大的支持，
like a React or a Vue, they've built up in such a strong way, with a big backing,
打字稿来自微软，流量来自Facebook。
TypeScript being from Microsoft, Flow being from Facebook.
他们与社区建立了如此庞大的关系
They've built up in such a big way with the community and
它背后的企业支持，学习和学习的投资
the corporate support behind it, that the investment to learn and
进入其中一个将会是一项长期回报的投资。
get into one of those is gonna be an investment that pays off for a long time.
下周不是什么时尚会消失。
It's not some fad that's gonna go away next week.
因此，受欢迎程度是一个强大的诉求。
So the popularity is a strong suit.
它背后有一个很大的社区，有大量的文档，
There's a big community behind it, a ton of documentation,
这些项目背后蕴藏着巨大的动力，这当然是有意义的。
a ton of momentum behind these projects, and it certainly does make sense.
其实我绝对会说，不管我喜欢不喜欢打字稿，
In fact, I would absolutely say, whether I liked TypeScript or not,
你在一个系统里工作对我来说是愚蠢的，
it would be silly to me for you to be working in a system,
假设您在Microsoft.NET商店工作，并且整天在后端编写C#，
say you worked in a Microsoft .NET shop and you wrote C# all day on the backend,
然后你需要做一些JavaScript。
and then you needed to do some JavaScript.
我无法想象你不会使用打字稿的情况。
I can't imagine a scenario where you wouldn't use TypeScript.
因为心理环境的转换，我一直在类型的世界和
Cuz the mental context switching of, I've been in types world and
现在我在非类型的世界里，会让我发疯的。
now I'm in non-types world, would be nuts to me.
因此，有很多情况下，它是完全有意义的。
So there's lots of scenarios where it makes completes sense.
它的受欢迎程度，这就是它不断增长的原因。
And the popularity of that, that's the reason why it's growing.
他们非常老练，这使他们非常擅长自己的工作。
And they're very sophisticated, and that makes them really good at what they do.
我真的有点惊讶于有多少像打字稿或者
I'm actually kind of amazed at how much something like TypeScript or
流可以从我甚至故意试图混淆的代码中推断出来，并且
Flow can infer from code that I even intentionally try to obfuscate, and
他们仍然能够搞清楚这些事情。
they're still able to figure those things out.
这些工具在这方面很棒。
These tools are fantastic at that.
所以这些都是很强的优点，但我也有一些强烈的负面影响。
So these are all strong pros, but I also have some strong negatives against them.